Hi, I'm Stan De Freitas, Mr. Green Thumb.
You know, if you start most of your house plants you need to have a good Watering Can, and normally you get something like this it's a little bit smaller than some of the watering cans that you've used outside on your vegetable garden area.
Something that's easy to work with.
Maybe it holds maybe a gallon, so it may be half the size of some of the bigger watering cans that you have used outside.
Make sure when you have one that you do have something that's going to apply to the end, so you can put that gentle stream of water onto your plants.
And you can see here it's got all the little holes, so we're going to put a nice little rain drop effect on for our little plants inside.
Most of our plants inside really can't take too much water.
If they get too hard a stream, well they may have a problem, especially true for African Violets, and Aglonemas.
Some of those plants, if they get too much water in one spot, you'll start to get into some fungal problems.
Make sure you apply this according to label directions when you apply any type of nutrient to your mix.
These are ideal if you're using a water-soluble plant food, or if you're using some type of fish emulsion.
Make sure you use it exactly according to those directions with your indoor watering can.
You'll have great results.
For On Gardening, I'm Stan De Freitas, Mr. Green Thumb.